内心的旅程很重要但也很危险,
The inner journey is important but also dangerous,
我需要进去看看我的内心,
I need to go in to find out what's on my heart,
我需要进去听听内在导师的声音。
I need to go in to hear the voice of the inner teacher.
但危险在于，
But the danger is that
我将只听到我想听到的东西，
I will hear only what I want to hear,
没有人在那里
that there will be no one
质疑我是否真的
there to question me about whether
听到了这些东西。
that's what I'm really hearing.
危险还在于我可能会听到
The danger also is that I might hear
一些深刻的真理，
something profoundly true,
但是因为没有其他人来讲述。
but by not having anyone else to tell it,
我有一个更好的机会忽略它,
I have a better opportunity to ignore it,
不听从那个声音。
to not follow that voice.
因此，我们希望人们在社区中
So we want people to take that inner journey in
进行这种内在的旅行，
community so that the community can ask
以便社区可以向他们提出那些可能
them those questions that might take
带他们深入自己的真理的问题，
them deeper into their own truth,
带他们穿过幻觉，带他们超越虚假，
take them past illusion and take them past falsehood
进入对他们来说更深刻的真理。
into what is more deeply true for them.
我们希望他们有一个社区，
And we want them to have a community
在这个社区里，他们可以说出
in which they can say the truths
他们所触及的真理，
that they have touched in a way
当你回去工作
that they makes it harder to forget those truths
或在生活中迈出下一步时，
when you go back to work or
他们会更难忘记这些真理。
when you take those next steps in your life.
我认为社区最古老的功能之一，
I think one of the most ancient functions of community
我们在结婚仪式上也这样做，不是吗？
and we do it in marriage ceremonies, don't we?
也就是说我们在这些朋友面前
It is to say we are making this private
做出这个私人承诺。
commitment in front of these our friends.
这应该是为了加强承诺，
And that's supposed to strengthen the
而且在许多方面确实如此，
commitment and in many ways it does,
当你在公共场合证明了一些事情时。
when you have attested to something communally.